Live Me, Love Me.
Hit Me, Hit Me.
Love Me, Love Me.
I think I've never felt enough to be.
I think we're still there.
I think we're all right.
I got a good thing.
Let's do that!
With me, I'm not sure.
I can't believe this!
I'm not yet. I don't accept it.
Shit, no mention of my fictures.
I'm not eh.
I'll give you something.
I'm not allowed to. I'm not allowed.
How much is it?
High tension
Love me!
Love me! Love me!
Love Don't be afraid to be a one-man
Don't be afraid to be a one-man Don't be
afraid to be a one-man Don't be afraid to
be a one-man Don't run
away Let's see you again
Kenjaku is going to
drop a bomb on the game,
and the Cullen game will
fulfill its real purpose.
I don't know what kind of
bomb Kenjaku is going to drop,
but it's going to happen in the
near future, that's for sure.
Maybe even this very moment.
That's why I'm preparing, by gathering
strong allies and stocking up points.
I have a few questions.
Is she strong enough
because I have my doubts?
It doesn't matter if she's strong,
because I'm just using her as bait
to attract other players here.
People tend to be less
wary of women, you know.
So when you're done using her,
you'll just kill her for the points?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'd never do that.
Even though you're a bust,
Reggie's my actual true knight.
As long as I serve him, he'll
protect me from all danger!
How naive and stupid.
David, do you and your allies possess at
least a hundred points between all of you?
Most certainly.
A new rule will be added soon.
It'll allow players to transfer
points between each other.
Hand over your points.
I need them for myself.
Seems like negotiations have broken down.
He's gone!
Hey!
No way.
Hey.
Don't let me see your face again.
Ah.
I get it, I get it.
I thought you were holding back,
but you can't kill us, can you?
You want our points, but
only if we give them to you.
But I think if you fight
without trying to kill,
You'll regret it the moment
you realize you're dead.
Hey!
I'm down here, too, you know!
You dead yet?
You good with this?
This smell!
Is it over?
Not yet.
Just like you.
He ran into a room
before the explosion hit.
Huh.
Not bad at all.
Good work.
I bet you wore him down a lot.
Do you finally get it?
They have no intention of protecting you.
Now you know.
So get out of here.
Give it a rest already.
Then...
say it.
Reggie said it when I asked him to!
He said he protected me!
He said he liked me!
So you say it!
I've seen them all.
Scumbags like you, who care more
about words than real action.
That was a heck of a throw.
But now you're all banged up.
Wasn't easy climbing back
up here, but I made it.
Use the stairs next time, Neanderthal.
Your attention please, your attention.
a player has added a new
rule to the culling game.
Rule number ten.
Players are able to
transfer a number of points
of their choosing to
other players in the game.
What kind of rule is that?
Max Elephant!
He did it again!
You bastard!
How dare you!
What am I doing?
I'll need more points in the future.
But Tsumiki won't be forced to
participate in the killing anymore.
Just be patient.
Believe in the others.
Don't obsess over these guys' points.
All I need to do is use my full might to
brush away any sparks
that might fall on me.
You have gained five points for a kill.
Man, what a waste of points.
How pathetic getting killed before
he could even use his technique.
Did Remy drop out?
Even so, it's still two on one.
Damn it, I'm still reeling
from that first explosion.
But fleeing's not an option.
Maybe I should use my domain.
Oh, bad idea.
It's still incomplete.
There's no way I can close the
barrier and trap them inside.
The worst outcome?
Would be them running off
and making me waste it.
Look out!
Out!
Out! Out!
Two on one huh i guess in your books
that's what you consider a fair fight.
Well not in mine where i'm from do you
know what they call people like you?
They call them cowards and
cowardly attacks won't work on me.
Behold!
Zero damage!
Young boy, I can help you.
I turned 35 this year.
With one look at someone's face, I can
tell if they're a good or bad person.
What's wrong?
Yikes!
Anyone ever tell you you
got one bad face? Uh-uh.
Oh, well.
I use a relative scale, just like schools.
Schools use absolute scales.
He did protect me.
So I guess I can trust him for now.
Well, how's Inoki?
What do you make of him?
I don't know the guy.
It's quicker.
I'll just ask him.
Hey, type, which are you?
I get it now.
You're asking what type of comedian I am.
A type that's always funny, or
the ones deluding themselves.
That's what you're asking, right?
Oh, I'm asking what arrow.
This costume is modeled after a hero,
the person who first made
me laugh my guts out?
when I was a child.
So to honor this costume, I cannot
allow my jokes to fall flat.
Here's a gag I just thought of.
Try using it on your
sweetheart if you have one.
Be ready for something.
Don't marry me.
I don't want you as my wife.
The End
He's fast.
His curse energy skyrocketed.
The shift in output is massive.
This guy is strong. Be careful!
I'm an old-school
entertainer who just recently
took a strong like it to extreme violence.
Now, do you want my help, young boy?
Once you and I take one of those
guys each, the younger guy, look,
he can turn his body parts into bombs.
And he's using reverse curse technique.
Dude!
Kogane! Yes?
Hiromi Higuruga's info, now!
Itadori's the one who added that rule.
I've decided that I'm
done with this colony.
Back down and I'll let you go.
Huh?
Where do you think you stand in this game?
I'm still owed points.
The ones I lost when you
killed Hari before I could.
Hey, guy.
The name's Takaba.
If you try to kill that
bomb bastard, if you can?
steal his points before you do.
Okay then, young boy.
I'll join you.
Let's fight with honor.
But I am an entertainer.
Whatever I do has got to entertain.
As long as you win, I really don't care.
Mm-hmm.
Smoking!
What a dangerous technique! Bam! Hurrah!
Don't worry!
When it comes to variety shows... Ah!
Birdie!
Red is prohibited.
That's funny!
Glad you are my enemy, Takaba.
Now there's a line I
always wanted to hear!
Later young boy try not to die oh
now that guy's dead too after that
humiliation Hazenoki's about to
crush your friend I think you should
worry about yourself I warned you
like I said I've achieved my objective
in this colony so no more holding
back I can fight for real now Hmm.
Max Elephant
Wow, didn't know they came that big?
Woo-hoo-hoo!
Woo-hoo!
Yeah!
Uh-huh!
Uh-huh-huh!
Uh-huh-huh! Uh-huh!
Uh-huh-huh-huh!
Ah-hoo-hoo!
You figured out my technique, haven't you?
But a water attack is pretty
simplistic, don't you agree?
You manifest whatever's on those receipts,
but there's more to it than that, right?
You're absolutely correct.
It's hard to describe, but I'd
call it free-enacting contracts.
For example, I can do this, too.
Contractual recreation.
What just burned in my hand
was a receipt for a Third,
two-night stay at the five-star
traditional inn Hoshizorate.
In other words,
my body is now as refreshed
as it would be after a restful
and relaxing vacation in a hot
springs resort for three days,
two nights,
plus massage.
I wonder how you're faring in comparison.
No doubt you have injuries from Earlier
and you've employed multiple shikigami?
Why you must be exhausted.
I often employ multiple shikigami at once.
The problem is that one of those was
Max Elephant which I usually use alone.
You can rapidly shuffle through shikigami
but not once they're injured. Right?
That's why you can't use your
dog to run, attack and defend.
And because of that you've been forced to
use multiple one trick
shikigami all at once.
It's a battle of attrition where neither
of us can use big high output moves.
Don't you see? It's futile.
There's no way you can kill me.
That's true.
So I'll run.
It won't be that easy.
A community gymnasium.
Did he flee inside or is he luring me in?
I could smoke him out with fire.
But getting into another
chase would be annoying.
Well, whatever shall I do?
Good.
It's just as I imagined.
This is the perfect size.
I wonder what you have planned for
me in here, you damned little punk.
You have something planned
yourself, don't you?
All sorcerers tend to
tell lies now and then.
Hyah!
Huh?
Ugh!
Ugh! Huh!
The things I recreate from
receipts are like Shikigami.
So I can give them simple
commands to get what I want.
Knives normally don't fly,
but that one should be.
Given your personality, I
think you're going to say no.
But if you transfer your points to me,
I promise I will give you
a quick and easy death.
Barrier techniques are
difficult, aren't they?
No matter how long I've tried,
I haven't been able to
get the hang of placing an
artificial space of
different size over reality.
Which is why.
No way.
I'm going to use this gymnasium
as is to deploy my domain.
He can do that.
Domain Expansion Chimera Shadow Garden
I didn't know he was a
sorcerer on that level
I never said I didn't have any big moves
I'm like a gift that I
can't believe in my soul.
I'm trying to find a way that
I can't believe in my soul.
You are cold.
The end of the day is coming.
What will it be like?
Thank you.
Even incomplete, a
domain is still a domain!
I'm pulling out my trump
card and activating it!
Not yet, and tour a little longer.
I acknowledge your strength.
Which of us will get crushed first?
GET CRUSHED!